acmoore.com 2019-06-24

# | A.C. Moore

This A.C. Moore Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use information you provide to us. By accessing or using this website, mobile application or other A.C. Moore product or service on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other electronic device that can access the web, you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy and warrant that all data provided by you is accurate and up to date. You are responsible for maintaining and promptly updating account information for accuracy and completeness.

Our goal is to provide you with more detailed and relevant information when it’s most meaningful to you and protect your data like it’s our own. 

To request modification or deletion of your personal data at any time, send us a note at dataprivacy@acmoore.com and we’ll gladly oblige. 

 _ **How we use your information**_

What we do depends on the information we collect during your visits and so we’ve outlined below why we do what we do in detail. 

 **Name and contact details** are primarily used to deliver your purchases to you.  

We also keep you up to date with information about our new products and services on acmoore.com and show you adverts as you browse the web.   

 **Your payment information** is collected so that we can perform our services and get your orders to you! Don’t worry, we do not store this information and use secure tokenization methods that allow you to come back to A.C. Moore and not have to re-enter the same information twice (unless you want to, of course, in which case you can always edit your payment methods).  

What’s tokenization, you ask? It’s a security technology that replaces sensitive account information, such as the 16-digit account number, with a unique digital identifier called a token. The token allows payments to be processed without exposing actual account details that could potentially be compromised.   

 **Your contact history** provides customer support and allows our relationship with you to be successful. We also use your history with us to train our team and get to know you, as well as ensure you get the best possible support no matter who gets the opportunity to help you.   

 **Your purchase history** and saved items also help us provide you with support and helps us stock up on items we think you and other customers may like.   

 **Information about your phone, laptop, browser, and how you use our services** gives us the ability to provide you with a great shopping experience.   

Whenever you browse or shop our site, you are giving us information that includes your IP address and device type, and certain actions you take on our site tell us how you’re using the site, as well.   

When you choose to share your location data with us we use it to improve our default options for you (such as currency) in order to give you the best possible shopping experience. We also use this information to protect you and our website against fraud.   

 **Information from accounts you link to us** makes it easier for you to sign up or login to acmoore.com. When you log into our website via your Facebook account you can quickly access shopping deals without having to create a specific account.   

 **Your responses to surveys, competitions and promotions** provide us with feedback that helps us improve our services and gives you an opportunity to win!   

 **It is always your choice** on whether or not you give us any of this personal information or visit our site. We treat your data like we would want ours treated and so we anonymize and aggregate personal information so that it does not identify you. We use it for purposes of testing our IT systems, data analysis, improving acmoore.com, and developing new products or services. We also share this information with third parties.  

 **Sharing your information** does not mean we sell your personal data to **any** third party. We do not and will never sell any of your personal data to any third party as we believe in building and maintaining your trust in us.   

 **When we share your information** with third parties it is because we believe it is an essential part of being able to provide our services to you. The following categories of companies help us ensure we’re running our business as effectively as we can:   

     • Companies that assist us with getting your purchases to you, such as payment service providers, warehouses, fulfillment centers, and delivery companies

     • Law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies 

     • Companies affiliated with ACMooreCommerce LLC

     • Professional service providers, such as marketing agencies, advertising partners and website hosts 

     • Companies approved by you, such as social media sites (if you choose to link your accounts to us) and PayPal where you choose to use their payment services    

 **Marketing communication** you opted to receive by email, SMS, or via your web browser can be turned off by you at any time. If you turn off or adjust the amount of marketing communication you receive from us, it may take multiple days for you to stop receiving this communication from us due to previously scheduled communications. You may edit your marketing communication by signing into your account and adjusting your settings, by visiting <https://acmoore.com/account/subscription> or by emailing us at customerservice@acmoore.com.  

Communication regarding orders you place with us will be sent by default to make it easier to track and ensure deliverability of your shipments. To opt out of receiving all communications from A.C. Moore you may use the unsubscribe link embedded at the bottom of our emails or email us with a request to unsubscribe from all emails at customerservice@acmoore.com.   

 **Seeing ads for A.C. Moore** online may occur when you’re visiting sites unaffiliated with us.   

We advertise throughout the world wide web using ad exchanges and marketing networks to create awareness of what we’re excited about and to help you see and find our products. We do this through a variety of methods, such as display and video advertising, and we use a range of advertising technologies like pixels, ad tags, web beacons, cookies, mobile identifies, Google analytics, as well as services offered by some sites and social networks, such as Custom Audience services offered by Facebook or other social media websites you’ve signed up for.   

We attempt to personalize the experience so that you find items you might like, and as such you will see banners or ads based on your previous use of acmoore.com. This is why you see advertising for products you previously clicked on while navigating the internet.   

 **We use Cookies** when you visit our site in order to improve site functionality and navigation. Below is how and why we use cookies, though please know that you have the ability to delete any cookies that are stored on your computer at any time. If you are not familiar with how to delete cookies, the “help” section in your web browser may provide instructions that can help.   

Cookies are used to improve site functionality and features we’ve designed to help you shop more efficiently upon return visits, or they can provide us with site analytics that help us improve site navigation. For example, you can save items for later that you added to your shopping cart, but were not yet ready to buy. We can also know which items are being clicked on so that we can show more or less of an item based on analytics cookies help us track.   

There are also customer preference cookies that will help remember things like your location or preferred currency, which helps us show you more relevant products or content.   

We also attempt to measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns through targeting or advertising cookies.   

By using our site, you agree to us placing cookies on your device and accessing them when you visit the site when you come back to us.   

 **We may change this page** periodically to reflect adjustments with how we are processing your data. If we make significant changes, we will make that clear on the A.C. Moore website or by other means of contact such as email so that you are able to review the changes before you choose to continue visiting or using A.C. Moore services.    

Contact our privacy team by emailing us at dataprivacy@acmoore.com or through our [Help Center](https://support.acmoore.com/hc/en-us) via the A.C. Moore website.   

You may also write to us at:   

A.C. Moore attn: Data Privacy Team   

130 AC Moore Drive 

Berlin, NJ 08009 

USA   

 _Last updated 10.16.2018_
